Используемые компоненты и библиотеки.
Naughter -
	Defines the Interface for an MFC wrapper class for serial ports
	Defines the interface for a class to enumerate the serial ports installed on a PC using a number of different approaches
	Defines the interface for a class which supports auto closing of a handle via CloseHandle
	Defines the interface for a class which supports auto closing of a heap pointer allocated via HeapAlloc
	Defines the interface for a class which supports auto closing of a HMODULE via FreeLibrary and setting of the last Win32 error via SetLastError

Copyright (c) 2013 by PJ Naughter (Web: www.naughter.com, Email: pjna@naughter.com)
----------------------------------------------------------------

BASS 2.4.10
Copyright (c) 1999-2013 Un4seen Developments Ltd.
----------------------------------------------------------------

HyperLink static control. Will open the default browser with the given URL when the user clicks on the link.

Copyright Chris Maunder, 1997-1999 (cmaunder@mail.com)
Feel free to use and distribute. May not be sold for profit
----------------------------------------------------------------

Version Control Build System. This header file was created by VERBUILD v1.0.0            

Copyright(c) 2005-2007 Yeamaec Communication.Co,.Ltd.      
----------------------------------------------------------------

Visual Leak Detector. Import Library Header

Copyright (c) 2005-2011 VLD Team.  This library is free software
----------------------------------------------------------------

DiscoAPI  OziExplorerAPI

